("Complete Control" by The Clash playing)
♪They said, "Release Remote Control" ♪
♪ But we didn't want it on the label ♪
♪ They said, "Fly to Amsterdam" ♪
♪ The people laughed,
but the press went mad ♪
♪ Ooh-oh, someone's really smart ♪
♪ Ooh-oh, complete control,
yeah, that's a laugh ♪
♪ On the last tour, my
mates they couldn't get in ♪
♪ I'd open up the back door
but they'd get run out again ♪
♪ And at every hotel
we was met by the law ♪
♪ Come for the party, just to make sure ♪
♪ Ooh-oh, someones really smart ♪
♪ Ooh-oh, complete
control, not on this song ♪
♪ They said we'd be artistically free ♪
♪ When we signed that bit of paper ♪
♪ They meant "Let's make a lots of money ♪
♪ And worry about it later" ♪
♪ Ooh-oh, someones really smart ♪
♪ Ooh-oh, complete control ♪
♪ I don't trust you ♪
♪ so why trust me ♪
♪ All over the town spread fast ♪
♪ They're dirty, they're filthy ♪
♪ They ain't going to last ♪
♪ Control ♪
♪ C-O-N trol ♪
♪ Parent control ♪
♪ Control ♪
♪ Felling like a running at a damn train ♪
♪ C-O-N trol ♪
♪ This is the public speaking ♪
♪ Oh yeah, control ♪
♪ This is the public ♪
♪ C-O-N trol ♪